[Music]
I'm psyching myself up for this marathon
by really thinking about running
somewhere I can never imagine I know
it's going to be unlike any other race
but for any other terrain I've done so
it's really going to be different I'm
very excited about it because you know
it challenges me it excites me you know
that gonna be there it's not gonna be
familiar but you know I'm gonna really
try my best to really prepare listen to
tips from all the experts that I can get
the hold off and you just enjoy the
experience it worries and fears for this
coming into this race definitely it's
the elements so running is going to be
the familiar for me that actual motion
of running that's familiar but it's
really deterring the whole I worry about
my dear
I worry about my nutrition I worry about
all these things that might happen but
at the same time I'm also very confident
that I'm going to be given that I have
the best possible gear coming into it
best possible advice that's possible
sponsors best possible on really support
and I'm very blessed if I'm gunning for
first place I want to be first place but
you know because I have not been there
it's very hard to assume or even be to
say because I've never gone to that part
of the world what I'm sure of is
I'm gonna do my best maybe try to make
my countrymen college mother